Stewart L. Udall papers, 1950-2010
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Department of the Interior, 1961-1972
  - The Department of the Interior, 1960-1961
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Recreation Congress, Detroit, Michigan. Includes Tape Recording. October 4, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Trinity Dam, California. October 14, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies- National Meeting of Superintendents of the Bureau of Indian Affairs, Denver, Colorado: Includes Tape Recording of Press Conference on October 17. October 16-18, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Banquet Honoring Stewart Udall Sponsored by the Montana State Young Democratic Club and the Yellowstone County Central Democratic Committee, Billings Montana. Includes Tape Recording. October 18, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Reclamation Association Meeting, Billings, Montana. Includes Tape Recording of Press Conference. October 19, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Saline Water Conversion Plant, Webster, South Dakota. October 20, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies. 1961 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      White House Regional Conference, Denver, Colorado, November 13, 1961
      White House Regional Conference, Seattle, Washington, November 20, 1961
      Octagon House Plaque Dedication, Washington, DC, November 27, 1961
      National Petroleum Council Meeting, Washington, DC, November 28, 1961
      Haskell Institute, Special Assembly Program, Lawrence, Kansas, December 3, 1961
      Pageant of Peace and Christmas Tree Lighting, Washington, DC, December 20, 1961
      Western Resources Conference at Colorado State University, Fort Collins, Colorado, 1961
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies-Trip to Japan, Joint United States-Japan Committee on Trade and Economic Affairs. Includes Stewart Udall's Climb up Mount Fuji: See also Box 177 (Oversize) for Framed and Inscribed Photo. November 1-7, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies. November 14-19, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Trip to Arizona Indian Advisory Committee Meetings, Phoenix, Tucson, etc.
      Arizona Conservation Council, Phoenix Salute to Hughes Aircraft Luncheon, Tucson
      Sunday Evening Forum, Tucson
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies-Arkansas State Electric Cooperative Meeting, Little Rock, Arkansas. December 4, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies-Trip to the Virgin Islands. December 8-10, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events & Ceremonies-Coal Mining Institute of America Meeting, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. December 14, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Speeches, Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Detroit, Michigan. March 4, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Speeches. March-May 1961 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Salt Lake City, Utah
      Tuscaloosa, Alabama
      Women's National Democratic Club, Washington, DC
    - Department of the Interior: Political Speeches. June 1961 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      Lewiston, Idaho
      Tacoma Washington
      Portland, Oregon
      Includes Trip to Mount Ranier
    - Department of the Interior: Political Speeches-Missouri, Ohio, Iowa, Vermont, West Virginia, New Jersey, New Mexico. September- December 1961 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Speeches, Background, Speech Material, etc. 1961 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - The Department of the Interior, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: 1962 Calendar. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Appointment Schedule. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 2-5)
    - Department of the Interior: Travel Accounts, Fiscal Year 1961/62. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Reports to the President. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President Kennedy. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President's Staff. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Staff. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Staff Meetings, Topics Discussed. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Interior: Jobs and Appointments, Letters of Recommendation. Includes Letter from Supreme Court Justice William O. Douglas Regarding Edward C. Crafts; and Letter from Eleanor Roosevelt Regarding Bruce McGaughey. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Personal and Miscellaneous Correspondence. Includes the Scott Turner Letter to President Kennedy Regarding "a place to play" Forwarded to Stewart Udall. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Interior: Photographs, Miscellaneous of Stewart Udall and Others. 1962 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Department of the Interior: Visit of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics Power Specialist. May 17-June 10, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Interior: Resources Program Staff, Reports etc. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Miscellaneous Reports from Various Divisions. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Miscellaneous. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Status of Legislation. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: "Howls from the Lunatic Fringe." 1962 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - Department of the Interior: Arizona Problems. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Summer Jobs. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Television Programs. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Press Conferences. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 10-11)
    - Department of the Interior: Cabinet Meetings. 1962 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Notes and Comments. 1962 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: President Kennedy's Message on Conservation to Congress. See also Box 178-John F. Kennedy Folder. March 1, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Budget: See also Box 178-John F. Kennedy Folder. 1962 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Department of the Interior Proposed Legislative Program, 88th Congress, 1st Session. November 1962 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings. 1962 (Box 100, Folder 6-10)
      Stewart Udall
      President Kennedy
      Congress
      Cuba
      Russia and the United States
      Inter-Cabinet Briefing Book
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies. January-February 1962 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      Conference on Land and People, Washington, DC, Janueary 15, 1962
      Department of the Interior Honor Awards Convocation, Washington, DC, January 18, 1962
      Wreath-laying, Lincoln Memorial, Washington, DC, February 12, 1962
      Presentation of "Plow" to President Kennedy, Commemorating the Homestead Act, White House, February 13, 1962
      Luncheon Honoring Senator Carl Hayden on His 50th Anniversary as a Member of Congress, Washington, DC, February 19, 1962
      Brotherhood Week Ceremonies, Washington, DC, Presentation of Award to President Kennedy by the National Conference of Christians and Jews (White House) and Dinner Address by Stewart Udall, February 19, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-League of Ohio Sportsmen Convention, Columbus, Ohio. Includes Tape Recording. February 10, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      Remarks of Stewart Udall before Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Supplemental Hearing on S. 2246-Water Planning Act, March 2, 1962
      Democratic Professional Club Meeting, San Diego, California, March 9, 1962
      Dedication of Buck Island Reef National Monument, Virgin Islands. Stewart Udall Does Under-Water Ribbon Cutting, March 1962
      Saline Water Conversion Conference, Washington, DC, March 28, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-National Rural Electric Cooperative Association Convention, Atlantic City, New Jersey. March 5, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-National Wildlife Federation Meeting, Denver, Colorado. March 9, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-Dedication of Saline Water Conversion Plant, San Diego, California. March 10, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies- Dedication of Fort Cobb Dam: Anadarko, Oklahoma. January 12, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-Wabash Valley Conservation Seminar, Terre Haute, Indiana. March 23, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-Presentation of Congressional Medal to Robert Frost by President Kennedy (White House). Includes Tape Recording. See also Box 224 for Film. March 26, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events, and Ceremonies-Robert Frost's 88th Birthday Party, Washington, DC. March 26, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior2: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Opening of the Cherry Blossom Festival, Washington, DC, April, 4, 1962
      Democratic Non-Partisan League Convention, Bismarck, North Dakota, April 13, 1962
      Conference of Atlantic Coast Governors with Federal Officials on Long-Range Shore Protection, Atlantic City, New Jersey, April 18, 1962
      Testimonial Luncheon honoring Senator Wayne Morse, Washington, DC, April 24, 1962
      Hike along the C and O Canal, Washington, DC, April 29, 1962
      Ramp Festival, Cosby, Tennessee, April 29, 1962
      Independent Petroleum Association of American Meeting, Kansas City, Missouri, April 30, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Signing of Order Establishing the Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, Washington, DC. April 2, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies- Philadelphia Conservationists Meeting, Philadelphia, PA. April 6, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies- Opening Baseball Game at New Stadium, Washington, DC. April 9, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Young Presidents Organization Meeting, Phoenix, AZ. April 10, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      Executive Luncheon of the Bureau of Yards and Docks, Department of the Navy, Washington, DC, May 1, 1962
      Fish Flour Luncheon, Washington. DC, May 10, 1962
      Department of Agriculture Annual Honor Awards Ceremony, Washington, DC, May 18, 1962
      Medicare Rally sponsored by Labor Unions, Kansas City, Missouri, May 20, 1962
      World Trade Day Luncheon, New York City, New York, May 23, 1962
      Department of the Interior Conservation Service Awards Ceremony, Washington, DC, May 25, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Commemoration of the 100th Anniversary of the Death of Henry David Thoreau, Dumbarton Oaks Park, Washington, DC. May 11, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-White House Conference on Conservation, Washington, DC. May 24-25, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 8-10)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      Dedication of Bituminous Coal Research Building, National Coal Association Convention, Monroeville, Pennsylvania, June 19, 1962
      Commemoration of the 375th Anniversary of the Birth of Virginia Dare and the 25th Anniversary of the "Lost Colony", Roanoke Island, Cape Hatteras, North Carolina, July 14, 1962
      Department of the Interior Annual Picnic, Fort. Hunt, Virginia, July 28, 1962
      Signing of Frying Pan-Arkansas Legislation, White House, August 16, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Trip to Fire Island, New York, and Nassau Democratic Dinner, Long Island, New York. June 2, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Stewart Udall Donation of Blood to the Red Cross, Washington, DC. June 5, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Dedication of Thornton Gap Interchange, Shenandoah National Park, and Birthday Party for Senator Harry F. Byrd, Virginia. June 9, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Signing Ceremony for the Navajo Irrigation Project, White House. June 13, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Ground-breaking Ceremonies for Sanford Dam, Canadian River Project, Amarillo, Texas: See also Box 177 (Oversize). June 30, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-First World Conference on National Parks, Seattle, Washington. June 30th-July 7th, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Trip to Maine (St. John-Allagash Area) and Speech at Fort Kent State Teachers College. July 6-8, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies: 10th- Dedication of Lincoln Boyhood National Memorial, Lincoln City, Indiana: See Also Box 179 for Wooden Plaque Presented to Stewart Udall by the Jaycees of Rockport, Indiana. July 1962 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies: 16th-22nd- Inspection Tour of Pacific Trust Territory Area; Southern Pacific Commission Conference, Samoa. July 1962 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies- Trip to Colombia, Inauguration of President G. Leon Valencia. Also Briefing Book. August 6-9, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-President Kennedy’s Western Trip. August 17-18, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 12-13)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      International Association of Game, Fish and Conservation Comissioners Convention, Jackson Lodge, Wyoming, September 9-11, 1962
      Signing Ceremony for Point Reyes, White House, September 13, 1962
      National Petroleum Council Meeting, Washington, DC, October 4, 1962
      McLean High School Leadership Conference, McLean, Virginia, October 6, 1962
      Wisconsin State Conservation Conference, Madison, Wisconsin, October 10, 1962
      Democratic Dinner, Rexburg, Idaho, October 17, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Dedication of Navajo Dam, Navajo Trail Highway, and Four Corners Marker, New Mexico: See Aalso Box 177 (Oversize). September 15-16, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Presentation of Land Addition to Gettysburg National Park, Pennsylvania. Includes Letters from and Photographs of Former President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Who Attended the Ceremony. September 20, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Trip to Alaska,Various Speeches and Meetings, Includes Chamber of Commerce, (Fairbanks) and Alaska Methodist University (Anchorage) and Letter from Oliver La Farge Regarding Alaskan Natives. September 23-28, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Ground-breaking for Norman Dam and Reservoir, Norman, Oklahoma. October 9, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Ground-breaking for Norton Dam and Reservoir, Norton, Kansas. October 11, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior, 1962: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies. 1962 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      National Electrical Manufacturers Association Meeting, Washington, DC, Nobember 14, 1962
      Joint Meeting, National Editorial Association Convention, Freedom of Information Conference, and Missouri Press Association Convention, St Louis, Missouri, November 16, 1962
      Dinner on Behalf of the National Cultural Center, Washington, DC, November, 29, 1962
      Joint Meeting United States-Japan Committee on Trade and Economic Affairs Meetings, Washington, DC, December, 3-5, 1962
      Council of State Governments, Chicago, Illinois, December 6, 1962
      Christmas Tree Lighting, White House, December 17, 1962
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Meeting of Great Swamp Committee of North American Wildlife Foundation, Sommerville, New Jersey. November 27, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events and Ceremonies-Stewart Udall Dinner Party for Russians: at which Mikoyan offered a Toast to "Our Children-May They Live in an Atomic-Free World." November 30, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Correspondence. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Stewart Udall’s Visit with Khrushchev. September 6, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Miscellaneous Notes by Stewart Udall. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Robert Frost. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, U.S. Clippings. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Union of Soviet Socialist Republics. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Photographs. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia: Background Information. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia: Official Report. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Trip to Russia, Various Reports. 1962 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, Stewart Udall and President Kennedy, His Staff, Robert Kennedy. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, General Correspondence. Includes Letter from Eric Sevareid. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, Stewart Udall Speech Notes and Background Material. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, Miscellaneous material. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, Clippings. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Political Campaign, Arizona Politics-Correspondence,Clippings. 1962 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Department of the Interior, 1963-1964
    - Department of the Interior: 1963 Calendar. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Appointment Schedule. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 2-5)
    - Department of the Interior: Travel Accounts, Fiscal Year 1962/63. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Reports to the President. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President Kennedy. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President's Staff. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Vice-President Johnson. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Staff. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Interior: Jobs, Appointments, Letters of Recommendation. Includes Letter from Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy Regarding S. Thomas Chandler as a Prospective District Judge in Arizona. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Personal and Miscellaneous Correspondence. Includes Letter from Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy Regarding Governor Wallace of Alabama. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Interior: Miscelleneous Photographs of Stewart Udall and Others. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Department of the Interior: National Park Service, Recreation Planning Analysis for Japan. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Interior: National Park Service, Resources Program Staff-Reports, etc. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Department of the Interior: National Park Service, Miscellaneous Reports from Various Divisions. 1963 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Department of the Interior: Visit of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics Power Specialist. 1963 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Department of Agriculture Study Tour of Agriculture in Eastern Europe-Report. 1963 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interio: "Howls from the Lunatic Fringe." 1963 (Box 108, Folder 3-4)
    - Department of the Interior: Summer Jobs. 1963-1964 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Television Programs. 1963 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Press Conferences. Includes Notebook Containing Summaries Compiled by Various Departments and Agencies on Progress During Two and One Half Years of the Kennedy Administration. Distributed from The White House. 1963 (Box 108, Folder 7-8)
    - Department of the Interior: Cabinet Meetings 1963 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Notes and Comments. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: President Kennedy, Death and Aftermath. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: President Kennedy, Clippings and Miscellaneous Speeches. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Budget. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Stewart Udall. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Miscellaneous. 1963 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. 1963 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      "Mona Lisa" Party, French Embassy, Washington, DC, January 8, 1963
      Reception and Dinner honoring Representative Michael J. Kirwan, Washington, DC, January 22, 1963
      American Cattlemen's Association Convention, Las Vegas, Nevada, January 30, 1963
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Death of Robert Frost, and Aftermath. January 29, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Stewart Udall's 43rd Birthday Party, Washington, DC. January 31, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. 1963 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      National Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts Convention, Denver, Colorado, February 5, 1963
      National Congress of American Indians, White House, March 5, 1963
      Biennial Wilderness Conference, sponsored by the Sierra Club, San Francisco, California, March 9, 1963
      Remarks of Stewart Udall before the National Advisory Board Council for Public Lands, Washington, DC, March 11, 1963
      National Petroleum Council Meeting, Washington, DC, March 22, 1963
      Dinner honoring Harold Wilson M.P.. British Embassy, Washington, DC, March 30, 1963